

# **BRIJESH SINGH**

### SYSTEMS ENGINEER, INFOSYS LTD

#### SUMMARY

I am an SDET-Java Tester with 1.5 yrs of experience. During this period I was part of the Mobile & Web Testing team. I also have an experience as a Front-end developer in the design, development, and maintenance of websites and web applications. I am proficient in HTML, CSS, Js, and also have a working knowledge of React.

#### PERSONAL DETAILS

# Birth date

05-02-1999

## Nationality

INDIAN

#### **Address**

Chandigarh, India

# CONTACT

- singh.brijesh.7696@gmail.com
- 08778656063
- https://brijesh\_singh.netlify.app/
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/brijeshsingh-atinfosys/
- https://github.com/coderbrijesh

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

# Systems Engineer

INFOSYS LTD

Mar, 2022 - Till Date

- Experience in designing and creating automation frameworks using Java, Selenium WebDriver, Rest Assured, Junit, TestNG, Maven, and Jenkins.
- Experience in Creating, Modifying, and Maintaining new and existing Automation Frameworks.
- Experience of API Service Level testing for web services, enhanced the Test harness and developed many Test suites using XML and JSON.
- Experience in bug tracking tools JIRA and code management tools GitHub.
- · Experience in writing moderate SQL queries for data validation.
- Experience in the Preparation of Test Execution Reports, Defect Reports, and Test Summary reports.
- · Experience in WebService testing using SOAP UI and Rest Assured

# Technical Associate

TECH MAHINDRA

Jun, 2021 - Mar, 2022

Responsible for testing the software application and troubleshooting and conducting regular tests and maintenance to ensure a smooth workflow.

# Business Development Associate

PLANETSPARK LTD

Feb, 2021 - Jun, 2021

- Successfully met my weekly sales targets by 90% to 400% week on week of Online Class packages.
- Maintained a retention rate of 95% through customer engagement and one-stop customer support.
- Scripted and tested direct sales process; increased closing customers by 30% month on month.
- Grew online sales by 30% week on week by effectively using sales techniques such as cold calling, Problem-solving, Need Generation, Negotiation, and Building Customer Relations.

# **EDUCATION**

# Bachelor Of Technology

HINDUSTAN UNIVERSITY, CHENNAI

2016-2020

XII

KV AFS AVADI, CHENNAI

2015-2016

X

ARMY PUBLIC SCHOOL FARIDKOT CANTT, PUNJAB

2013-2014

# **TECHNOLOGY SKILLS**

Java Core & SE	8 HTML	CSS J	avaScript	React	Node	.js N	Mongo Db	MySQL
Selenium IDE	Cucumber	SOAP UI	Postmar	n API	Maven	Jenki	ns C++	С
Azure AZ 900	Azure Al 900	SCRUM						

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

- Infosys Certified Selenium Advance
  Automation Tester
- Microsoft Certified: Azure Al Fundamentals
- Infosys Global Agile Developer Certification
- Scrum Foundation Professional Certificate -SEPC™
- Infosys Certified Selenium Basic Automation Tester
- Microsoft Certified: Azure Fundamentals
- Scrum Fundamentals Certified (SFC)
- ✓ IBM Cloud Core